Peter Farrow

I am a full-stack web developer currently based in Salt Lake City, Utah. I am looking to work somewhere I can keep learning and growing with constructive feedback. I was a professional contemporary dancer and teacher for 6 years, and still have a passion for all kinds of art.

375 E Logan Ave Salt Lake City, UT 84115 1 (804) 840-8219 pnfarrow@gmail.com Portfolio LinkedIn

SELECTED EXPERIENCE

Dance Shows NYC | New York, NY (Remote) — Web Consultant

SEPTEMBER 2024 - PRESENT

Compiled data on dance performances to input into Airtable, as well as provided insight and feedback to the site's owners on UI/UX design and customer data management.

Devmountain | Lehi, UT (Remote) — Web Developer (Student)

MAY 2024 - NOVEMBER 2024

See Projects section for details.

Ririe-Woodbury Dance Company | Salt Lake City, UT — Dancer

JUNE 2021 - MAY 2024

Taught interactive dance classes for over 30,000 elementary school students per year. Performed in world-class contemporary dance productions across the USA, and organized audio for lectures and performances using Audacity and QLab.

GrowNYC | New York, NY — Market Manager

AUGUST 2020 - JUNE 2021

Organized a 20+ vendor farmers market each morning based on weather and traffic conditions and executed quick and smooth EBT transactions via iPad.

Sleep No More | New York, NY — Performer

JULY 2018 - FEBRUARY 2020

Performed in over 400 immersive dance-theater shows for 100,000+ total audience members. Excelled at multitasking in a high-stress environment by executing difficult choreography in close proximity to the audience, and adapted quickly to working with new partners and scene-mates with little preparation.

EDUCATION

 ${\bf Devmountain} \mid {\bf Lehi, UT \ (Remote) - \it Web \ Development \ Certificate}$

MAY 2024 - NOVEMBER 2024

The Juilliard School | New York, NY — BFA in Dance

AUGUST 2014 - MAY 2018

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

React

Express.js

PostgreSQL

Git

Bootstrap

Postman

Axios

Redux

Airtable

PROJECTS

Maestro Playlist Creator

Utilized the Spotify API to fetch, display, and save music data based on the user's mood. Provided OAuth authentication using Spotify's Authorization Code flow. Worked in a collaborative team of four using Github Projects.

Mangrove Manor Mystery Game

Developed an interactive mystery game inspired by the *Choose Your Own Adventure* book series using a React front-end and an Express back-end. Created and seeded a PostgreSQL database using the Sequelize ORM.